datzhott.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy

**What[information](http://datzhott.com/2012/10/11/streaming-live-ignite-atlanta-official-a3c-festival-hip-hop-politics-panel/) do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter.

[Google](http://datzhott.com/2012/07/30/google-wants-good-in-the-hood-offers-fiber-high-speed-internet-and-tv-service/), as a third [party](http://datzhott.com/2012/05/21/mark-zuckerberg-changed-his-facebook-status-to-married/) vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of [the](http://datzhott.com/2010/11/01/mariah-carey-yes-we-are-pregnant/) DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their [visit](http://datzhott.com/2010/09/22/the-lbc-crew-which-way-is-up/) to your sites and other sites on the [Internet](http://datzhott.com/2012/07/30/google-wants-good-in-the-hood-offers-fiber-high-speed-internet-and-tv-service/).  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and [content](http://datzhott.com/2012/08/14/video-ball-up-life-on-the-road/) network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site [feature](http://datzhott.com/2012/07/30/google-wants-good-in-the-hood-offers-fiber-high-speed-internet-and-tv-service/)

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional [company](http://datzhott.com/2012/07/30/google-wants-good-in-the-hood-offers-fiber-high-speed-internet-and-tv-service/) [news](http://datzhott.com/2012/05/21/mark-zuckerberg-changed-his-facebook-status-to-married/), updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any [time](http://datzhott.com/2012/10/07/oh-snap-yale-students-make-millions-translating-hip-hop-lyrics/) you would like to unsubscribe from receiving [future](http://datzhott.com/2012/11/05/the-10-best-online-tools-for-millennial-voters/) emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your [Web](http://datzhott.com/2012/08/31/another-sad-day-in-hip-hop-mogul-chris-lighty-dies-from-apparent-suicide/) browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside[parties](http://datzhott.com/2012/09/17/kandi-burruss-opens-up-door-to-door-sex-toy-business/)?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our [business](http://datzhott.com/2012/09/17/kandi-burruss-opens-up-door-to-door-sex-toy-business/), or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also [release](http://datzhott.com/2012/07/30/google-wants-good-in-the-hood-offers-fiber-high-speed-internet-and-tv-service/) your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California[Online](http://datzhott.com/2011/10/06/steve-jobs-succumbs-at-56/) Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your [personal](http://datzhott.com/2013/03/12/beyonce-jay-z-kim-kardashian-and-more-hacked-hiphollywood-com/) information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from [anyone](http://datzhott.com/2012/09/17/kandi-burruss-opens-up-door-to-door-sex-toy-business/) under [13](http://datzhott.com/2012/08/31/another-sad-day-in-hip-hop-mogul-chris-lighty-dies-from-apparent-suicide/) years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.datzhott.com](http://www.datzhott.com/)

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online ](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/)privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to [change](http://datzhott.com/2012/10/11/streaming-live-ignite-atlanta-official-a3c-festival-hip-hop-politics-panel/) our privacy policy, we will [post](http://datzhott.com/2011/10/06/steve-jobs-succumbs-at-56/) those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 03/[16](http://datzhott.com/2012/10/11/streaming-live-ignite-atlanta-official-a3c-festival-hip-hop-politics-panel/)/[12](http://datzhott.com/2012/08/31/another-sad-day-in-hip-hop-mogul-chris-lighty-dies-from-apparent-suicide/)

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

[datzhott](http://datzhott.com/2010/09/22/the-lbc-crew-which-way-is-up/).[com](http://datzhott.com/2012/07/10/custom-id-justin-bieber-2013-uk-tour-tickets-on-sale-nowtue-10-jul-2012-003133-0700/)@gmail.com

This policy is powered by Trust Guard [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm).
